qiqutv.com 2014-04-06

# PRIVACY POLICY

Guangzhou Ming Yang Information Technology Co.,Ltd. takes all reasonable steps to protect the privacy of you and ensure that your personal information we collect is not ordinarily disclosed to third parties without your consent. However, there may be times when Guangzhou Ming Yang Information Technology Co.,Ltd. may be required to disclose personal information of you without your express consent. This may occur where we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against you or another person who may be causing injury to, or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally), the rights or property of Guangzhou Ming Yang Information Technology Co.,Ltd. or its associates, affiliates, other customers or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; or required by law. We are firmly committed to privacy. Third parties may be using web beacons or similar technologies to collect information in the course of ads being served on this site. For more information pertaining to end users' options for cookie management, please refer [here](http://support.google.com/adsense/bin/static.py?hl=en&gl=US&client=ca-dp-gzd-d&ts=1631343&page=ts.cs&rd=1&contact=abg_afc).Our use of your personal information is regulated as follows:

* * *

## 1\. I.P. Address

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to audit the use of our site. When guests request pages from our sites, our servers may log the guests' IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our terms of service; or to protect our service, site, you or others.

* * *

## 2\. Links to Other Sites

Users should be aware that on our affiliated websites, there are links to third party websites. Neither Guangzhou Ming Yang Information Technology Co.,Ltd. nor its subsidiaries have any control over this and hence, accepts no responsibility for the content of these sites, or the actions of the operators, in relation to the collection of personal information of users of these sites. While Guangzhou Ming Yang Information Technology Co.,Ltd., our associates and affiliates, make every effort to protect your personal information and your privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online, that information can be collected and used by people that neither of us may know. And also our site may contain hyperlinks to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third-party sites.

* * *

## 3\. Cookies. 

Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. We allow advertisers and other business partners to place cookies onto your computer when you visit this website. These cookies are placed to keep track of the web searches you make while visiting this website, as well as your web surfing behavior on this website and other websites you may visit. That information is used to show you advertisements tailored to your interests on this and other websites, and/or to keep track of your response to each ad. While we do use cookies in other parts of Our Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by an ad company. That ad company, and not us, has exclusive control of and access to the information it collects. 

* * *

## 4\. Permitted Disclosures. 

We may disclose personal information about you to third parties when the disclosures have been specifically authorized by you or when we believe, in the good faith, that such disclosures are reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, dispute resolution process, or to comply with or enforce this Agreement.

* * *

## 5\. Your Acceptance of These Terms 

By using this website or our affiliated websites, you signify your assent to the terms and conditions contained herein (as amended from time to time). If you do not agree to be bound by its terms, we politely ask that you do not use this site.
